Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Historical Materials Collection
1819 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts College
Tufts University
UA136
175.36 Linear Feet 188 boxes and 48 oversize folders
7 Volumes
6 Artifact(s)
1503 Digital Object(s)
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Artifacts and ephemera; Photographs; Books; Audio Lab materials; University audiovisual materials; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Since 1955, Tufts University has continued to expand its horizons. In 1964, in one of Wessell's final acts as president, Tufts opened the Experimental College. The Ex-College, which allows students to take classes not normally found in the curriculum, has remained one of Tufts' most popular programs.
In 1977, Tufts established a five-year joint degree program with the New England Conservatory of Music. Soon after, in 1979, a similar program began with the School of the Museum of Fine Arts. Also in 1979, the Tufts Center for European Studies in Talloires, France, was established in an 11th Century priory. The Tufts European Center began operation soon after.
In late 1979, Tufts made another important addition. In October, the Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine opened at its original Boston campus. In 1980, the Grafton campus, built on the site of a state mental hospital, officially opened its doors.
The last two major additions to Tufts University took place in 1980 and 1981. In 1980, the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, established with a large grant from the Sackler family, opened its doors on the Boston campus of the Tufts School of Medicine. In 1981, at the Medford Campus, Tufts celebrated the opening of the School of Nutrition Science and Policy. The school was the first of its kind in the nation.
Since Tufts College was officially established in 1852, it has continued to grow and expand in new directions. From its beginnings as a small liberal arts college through its expansion into a full-scale university, Tufts has maintained a strong academic tradition and a community feel.
Custodial History
The materials in this collection have minimal provenance documentation. Digital Collections and Archives staff move objects from this collection into other more appropriate collections when provenance is positively identified.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials including artifacts, ephemera, memorabilia, ledgers, loose photographic prints, and audio and visual material relating to Tufts history for which no provenance can be assigned.
The Audio Lab series contains lectures, panels, conferences, and performances at Tufts circa 1960-2000. Notable speakers include Ralph Nader, F. Lee Bailey, Robert Klein, Maya Angelou, Noam Chomsky, George McGovern, Dr. Benjamin Spock, Coretta Scott King, Allen Ginsberg, Timothy Leary, Stokely Carmichael, William F. Buckley, Margaret Mead, Muhammed Ali, Jane Fonda, Joe Biden, Norman Mailer, Isaac Asimov, P.J. O'Rourke, Jimmy Carter, Haruki Murakami, Margaret Thatcher, and many other prominent social and political figures.
University history; Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts; Student life; Finance
- Artifacts and ephemera, 1861 -- 2012; UA136.001; 18.1 Linear Feet; 4 Volumes; 1 Artifact(s); 90 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains memorabilia and objects relating to the history of Tufts that could not be assigned to other collections.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as found.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Copies of wills and correspondence regarding wills and bequests, 1861 -- 1890; UA136.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Walker, William J.; Wade, John; Packard, Sylvanus; Winn, Maria; Fay, Harriet; Dean, Oliver; Felton, Cyrus; Hunt, Ebenezer; Bement, William; Dockstader, George A.; Skinner, Cornelia B.
  - Tufts College treasurer's ledger, 1876 -- 1904; UA136.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Tufts College treasurer's ledger, 1906-08-01; UA136.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Tufts bookmark, UA136.001.003.00003 (Box Shared 81)
    light green linen bookmark
  - Tufts College treasurer's ledger, 1909-10-01; UA136.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College treasurer's ledger, 1943; UA136.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Diplomas, certificates, and bonds, 1861 -- 1962; UA136.001.006
    - Catherine Elizabeth Brannick's M.D. diploma, 1916; UA136.001.006.00001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Charles Justin McKenzie's diploma, 1868; UA136.001.006.00002 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - War certificate and Tufts War Service Bond, WWI, 1918; UA136.001.006.00003 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Olive Barrow's B.A. diploma, 1924; UA136.001.006.00004 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - William McHenry Franklin's Ph.D. diploma, 1941; UA136.001.006.00005 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Cora Polk Dewick's Tufts College Distinguished Service Key certificate, 1948; UA136.001.006.00006 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Frederick Gowing's B.A. diploma, 1881; UA136.001.006.00007 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Cora Alma Dewick's honorary M.A. diploma, 1944; UA136.001.006.00008 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Cora Polk Dewick's honorary Ph.D. diploma, 1952; UA136.001.006.00009 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Herbert R. Hearsey's B.S. diploma, 1934; UA136.001.006.00010 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Herbert R. Hearsey's M.A. diploma, 1934; UA136.001.006.00011 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Grace Inez Wheeler's B.A. diploma, 1905; UA136.001.006.00012 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Charles Harlow Woodbury's B.A. diploma, 1905; UA136.001.006.00013 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Delta Upsilon membership certificate for Charles Dunn Cushing, 1910; UA136.001.006.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Alonzo Ames Miner, honorary degrees and New England Historic-Genealogical Society membership, 1861; UA136.001.006.00015 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
      Honorary degrees and membership certificates are from different years.
    - James Tremante, Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering, 1947; UA136.001.006.00016 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Roland Leonard Eaton, Bachelor of Arts degree, 1917; UA136.001.006.00017 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Edmond Spencer, Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering degree, 1920; UA136.001.006.00018 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Earle Trull Wentworth, Jr., School of Medicine doctorate, 1949; UA136.001.006.00019 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Samuel Figler, Doctorate, School of Dentistry, 1938; UA136.001.006.00020 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - John Elmer Eklund, Bachelor of Science, Civil Engineering degree, 1932; UA136.001.006.00021 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Frederic Tudor Farnsworth, M.A. diploma, 1876; UA136.001.006.00022 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Frederic Tudor Farnsworth, B.A. diploma, 1873; UA136.001.006.00023 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Ray Dwinell Farnsworth, B.A. diploma, 1908; UA136.001.006.00024 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    - Benjamin Franklin Thompson, Bachelor of Science, Electrical Engineering degree, 1891; UA136.001.006.00025 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
      This is a gift donated by his great-grandson, Peter R. Thompson.
    - Alonzo Ames Miner, Theologiae Doctorem, Harvard University, 1863; UA136.001.006.00026 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
      Miner received an honorary Doctor of Theology from Harvard in 1863. This diploma was found with other uncataloged historical items, July 2007.
    - Tufts College Bonds and Trustee of Tufts College Dormitory Bond, 1924 -- 1952; UA136.001.006.00027 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
      The 1926 Tufts College Bond for Roger Frederick Etz (A'09) was found with other un-cataloged historical items in July 2007. The 1926 Tufts College Bond for Morris M. Danovitch (E'24), the anonymous bond script (1924), and the Dormitory Bond (1952) were donated by the Office of Alumni relations. The circa 1920-1930 Tufts College Bond for Howard Edwin Grupe was donated by Paula Coyle in December 2018.
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      The circa 1920-1930 Tufts College Bond for Howard Edwin Grupe was a gift of Paula Coyle, 2018, accession UA-2019-053.
    - Tufts University Library Day Certificate, 1962; UA136.001.006.00028 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
      This item was found with other uncataloged historical items, July 2007.
    - Lexington (M.A.) Monument Association Rev. A.A. Miner D.D, UA136.001.006.00029 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
      Certificate to Alphonsum Ames Miner
  - Ephemera and honorary degree translation, 1880 -- 1990; UA136.001.007
    - "Tufts College Medley Overture" Arranged by George Swift with original box, ca. 1907, UA136.001.007.00001 (Box Shared 81)
      Donor unknown; This item is a player piano music roll; written on the box and music roll is the following "Eighty-Eight Note 300503 Tufts College Medley Overture Introducing: (1) Around the Rez; (2) Aren't You Glad You're a Tufts Man? (3) I've Been Thinking; (4) Brown and Blue; (5) The Jumbo Cantepic; (6) Hymn to College Hill; (7) The Barnum Song; (8) For Tufts, Hurrah!; (9) Keep Your Eye on Tufts; (10) Tufts Victory Song; (11) Dear Alma Mater; (12) Forward, Tufts! Arranged by George Swift"
    - Tufts postcards, 1907 -- 1949; UA136.001.007.00002 (Box Shared 81)
      15 postcards and 4 notecards depicting buildings on the Tufts Medford campus. Date is approximate
      Buildings
    - Tufts bookmark, UA136.001.007.00003 (Box Shared 81)
      Silk bookmark with college seal. No Date Available
    - Jackson College tea room teacup, UA136.001.007.00004 (Box Shared 81)
      White teacup from the Jackson College tea room, now the Jackson gym dance studio. Donated by Kyna Hamill in 2006. No Date Available
    - Tufts Boston Club By-Laws, Tuftonian Receipt, and Library Subscription Letter, 1880 -- 1885; UA136.001.007.00005 (Box Shared 81)
      Donated by Jane M. Hennedy of the the Old Colony Historical Society (accession 2008.056); Materials possibly belonged to L. E. White; Tufts College Club of Boston By-Laws from 1880, Letter announcing for first meeting of the Tufts Boston Club, Receipt for a year long subscription to the Tuftonian, and Letter requesting alumni subscriptions in support of the library fund.
    - Tufts College Rifle Club, congratulatory poster from The National Rifle Association of America, 1945-01-25; UA136.001.007.00006 (Box Shared 36)
      This item was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
      poster
    - Honorary degree translation, 1960; UA136.001.007.00007 (Box Shared 81)
      This date is approximate. This folder was found uncataloged in Winter 2008.
    - Pin and charms, 1931 -- 1935; UA136.001.007.00008 (Box Shared 81)
      Donated by Robert B. Spence. Materials belonged to Robert A. Spence, BSME 1935. Includes American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Tuft Chapter pin and charm.
      Mechanical engineering
    - Tufts checkbook, 1983; UA136.001.007.00009 (Box Shared 81)
      This item is being used in the spring 2012 reunion exhibit. Cover decorated with Tufts seal. This item was moved to this location from the Women's Center records UA156 during processing by Molly Bruce and Susanne Belovari in June, 2011.
    - Four postcards, 1955 -- 1970; UA136.001.007.00010 (Box Shared 81)
    - Tufts sweatshirt and receipt, 1990; UA136.001.007.00011 (Box Shared 81)
      The sweatshirt is being used in the spring 2012 reunion exhibit. Item was found in the Women's Center basement and removed from the Women's Center records UA156 during processing.
  - Commemorative Plates, 1932 -- 1957; UA136.001.008
    - Carmichael Hall, Tufts University, 1957; UA136.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - President's House, Tufts University, 1957; UA136.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Alumnae Hall, Tufts University, 1957; UA136.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Eaton Memorial Library, Tufts College, 1957; UA136.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Dedicated tablets, 1955; UA136.001.008.00005 (Box Shared 10)
      The tablet reads, "This tablet commemorates the devoted and inspired men and women who have served this university and its high purposes. They are the light Charles Tufts had in mind more than a century ago when he said I will set a light upon this hill. 1955".
    - Ballou Hall, 1932; UA136.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
      Donated by Donna Hersey Sandin.
    - Ballou Hall, 1942; UA136.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
      Donated by Donna Hersey Sandin. Signed by Leonard Carmichael.
    - College Edifice, 1957; UA136.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
      Donated by Donna Hersey Sandin. Signed by Nils Wessel.
    - President's House, 1957; UA136.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - President's House, 1957; UA136.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Donald Meeds Small's Tufts Academic Robe, 1908; UA136.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
    Donald M. Small graduated from Tufts Dental School in 1908 and was a trustee of Tufts. Robe donated by Small's daughter, P.S. Fessenden; includes some biographical material. Date given is date of his graduation from the Tufts Dental School and may not reflect the date of the robe.
  - Tufts Banner, 2000; UA136.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
    The Tufts banner was found uncataloged in the stacks in summer 2007. Date is approximate
  - Brass and Lead Type for Lettering Press and a tool, UA136.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
    Brass type has 0-9, letters A-Z in capitals and some lower case. Lead type has various letters. One tool is also in the box. Lettering press found uncatalogued with a "Simplex Goldstamping Press" in the stacks in the summer of 2007. Provenance is unclear. The "Simplex Goldstamping Press" remains in the stacks.
  - Lead type for Lettering Press and a tool, UA136.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
    Lettering press found uncatalogued with a "Simplex Goldstamping Press" in the stacks in the summer of 2007. Provenance is unclear. The "Simplex Goldstamping Press" remains in the stacks.
  - Tufts College Map of Grounds surveyed and drawn by the Engineering Classes Exhibited at the Centennial Exposition, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1876., UA136.001.014.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    This folder is filed in the oversize map drawer. This item was found with other uncataloged historical items, July 2007. Preservation notes 2007: paper mounted on fabric, mounted on board. edges of paper are crumbling.
  - Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity paddle and pledge book, 1947; UA136.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
    Donated by Philip Primack, belonged to his father, Joseph Primack
  - Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity pledge book, 1949; UA136.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Tufts crest teacup, 1942 -- 1989; UA136.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
    Exact date unknown. Donated by Philip Primack, belonged to his father, Joseph Primack
  - Scrimshaw box of Tufts buildings, 1989; UA136.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
    Created by Meetings, Etc., a coorporate gifts company. Donated by Philip Primack, belonged to his father, Joseph Primack
  - Four Tufts postcards, 1906 -- 1907; UA136.001.021.00001 (Box Shared 24)
    Gift of Jessica Villella.
  - Cigarette cards, 1904 -- 1930; UA136.001.021.00002 (Box Shared 24)
  - Leather flags and cards, 1904 -- 1930; UA136.001.021.00003 (Box Shared 24)
  - Tufts basketball and fencing fringed cloth ephemera, 1900 -- 1950; UA136.001.021.00004 (Box Shared 24)
  - Print of Professor Arthur Michael, 1898-06-01; UA136.001.021.00005 (Box Shared 24)
  - Print of Elmer S. Olmsted, 1898; UA136.001.021.00006 (Box Shared 24)
  - Print of Wilson T. Stowe, 1890 -- 1900; UA136.001.021.00007 (Box Shared 24)
    "T" could be a "P". Gift of Jessica Villella.
  - Cigarette company advertisement, 1904 -- 1930; UA136.001.021.00008 (Box Shared 24)
  - Cigarette boxes, 1904 -- 1930; UA136.001.021.00009 (Box Shared 24)
  - Plaque in honor of Edward E. Cohen given by a group of his friends, 1900 -- 1960; UA136.001.021.00010 (Box Shared 24)
    Gift of Jessica Villella. Screws are included. Accompanying note (included in envelope) says that the plaque was on the door of room 024 in basement of Aidekman and was removed in March 2006 before basement demolition. As of fall 2010, research indicates that room 024 was the Music Library annex but that the plaque predates that use of the room and it is therefore unclear who Edward E. Cohen was and for what the room was dedicated.
    Cohen, Edward E.
  - Tufts College: A Seat of Learning in New England, 1920 -- 1925; UA136.001.022.00001 (Box 22)
    Undated publication. A gift of Stan Robinson, class of 1950.
  - Tufts College: A Seat of Learning in New England, 1931; UA136.001.022.00002 (Box 22)
    A gift of Stan Robinson, class of 1950.
    Volume, issue
    31, 4
  - Tufts College [Pictorial book], 1927 -- 1950; UA136.001.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Winter campus scene and negative of male standing at gate, 1920 -- 1950; UA136.001.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Postcards, 1900 -- 1950; UA136.001.022.00005 (Box 22)
    Gift of Brent Jackson Estate
  - Coffin, Robert P. Tristman, 1936; UA136.001.022.00006 (Box 22)
    Coffin visited Tufts in 1940 and his poems have been published in Tufts publications.
  - Tufts College 1904, UA136.001.022.00007 (Box 22)
    Photograph booklet containing images of Tufts College from 1904. The booklet says, "Tufts College Publications New Series, Vol. IV, No. 5". It was donated by Glenda J. Jackson in November, 2011.
  - Tufts College 1907, UA136.001.022.00008 (Box 22)
    Photograph booklet containing images of Tufts College from 1907. The booklet says, "Tufts College Publications New Series, Vol. VII, No. 5". It was donated by Glenda J. Jackson in November, 2011.
  - Columbia space shuttle flag, 1981; UA136.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
    Flag and patch presented to Tufts University from Astronauts John Young and Robert Crippen.
  - Columbia space shuttle patch and certificate, 1981; UA136.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Patches for Peace plaque, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
    This item is being used in the spring 2012 reunion exhibit. This box contains the plaque that was displayed with the Patches for Peace quilt. The plaque displays the following message: "'Patches for Peace' was a campus-wide effort to respond in a hopeful way to the tragic events of September 11, 2001. Spearheaded by Tufts Hillel, 88 University organizations came together over the following months to construct a 96 square foot quilt that was unveiled on November 7th of the same year. The project symbolizes the united vision for peace the diverse members of the Tufts community share." The plaque also displays a list of the 88 students groups that participated in the Patches for Peace project.
  - Patches for Peace quilt, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
    "'Patches for Peace' was a campus-wide effort to respond in a hopeful was to the tragic events of September 11, 2001. Spearheaded by Tufts Hillel, 88 University organizations came together over the following months to construct a 96 square foot quilt that was unveiled on November 7th of the same year. The project symbolizes the united vision for peace the diverse members of the Tufts community share." Source: Patches for Peace plaque. UA136/001-026.00001. Collection documentation folder in UA136 includes a DVD by conservators.
    - Caribbean Club Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00001; Caribbean Club
      Patch is located on quilt at 10F
    - Strategic Gaming Society Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00002; Strategic Gaming Society
      Patch is located on quilt at 1A
    - Tufts Biology Society Patches for Peace quilt, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00003; Tufts Biology Society
      Patch is located on quilt at 1D
    - Tufts Symphony Orchestra Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00004; Tufts Symphony Orchestra
      Patch is located on quilt at 2B
    - Tufts Buddhist Society Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00005; Tufts Buddhist Society
      Patch is located on quilt at 2C
    - Miller Hall RA staff Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00006
      Patch is located on quilt at 2D
    - Tufts Crew Teams Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00007; Tufts Crew Teams
      Patch is located on quilt at 2E
    - Chi Omega Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00008; Chi Omega
      Patch is located on quilt at 16F
    - Alpha Phi Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00009; Alpha Phi
      Patch is located on quilt at 14F
    - Tufts Christian Fellowship Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00010; Tufts Christian Fellowship
      Patch is located on quilt at 2F
    - Ears for Peers Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00011; Ears for Peers
      Patch is located on quilt at 10E
    - Inter Greek Council Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00012; Inter Greek Council
      Patch is located on quilt at 9F
    - Omidyar Scholars Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00013; Omidyar Scholars
      Patch is located on quilt at 7F
    - TRUCE Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00014; TRUCE
      Patch is located on quilt at 2A
    - Tufts Tae Kwon Do Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00015; Tufts Tae Kwon Do
      Patch is located on quilt at 3B
    - Panhellenic Council Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00016; Panhellenic Council
      Patch is located on quilt at 3C
    - Tufts Hillel Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00017; Tufts Hillel
      Patch is located on quilt at 8D
    - Institute for Global Leadership Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00018; Institute for Global Leadership
      Patch is located on quilt at 3D
    - Italian Club Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00019; Italian Club
      Patch is located on quilt at 16E
    - Queen's Head and Artichoke Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00020; Queen's Head and Artichoke
      Patch is located on quilt at 3E
    - Simlab Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00021; Simlab
      Patch is located on quilt at 3F
    - International Club Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00022; International Club
      Patch is located on quilt at 16D
    - Outbreath Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00023; Outbreath
      Patch is located on quilt at 12C
    - Society of Women Engineers Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00024; Society of Women Engineers
      Patch is located on quilt at 4A
    - Tufts Friends of Falun Gong Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00025; Tufts Friends of Falun Gong
      Patch is located on quilt at 4D
    - Hawaii Club Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00026; Hawaii Club
      Patch is located on quilt at 4F
    - Shotokan Karate Club Patches for Peace quilt block, 2001-11-07; UA136.001.026.00003.00027; Shotokan Karate Club